Clara Magaldi Rodrigues

1602-88 Redpath Ave, Toronto, ON M4S 2J8 437-244-5929 claramagaldi@gmail.com

claramagaldi@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/clara-magaldi github.com/claramagaldi

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROGRAMMING SKILLS COLLABORATION LEADERSHIP

SUMMARY

I am a graduate of Centennial College's 3-year Software Engineering Technology program with High Honours and am looking for an opportunity at **Capgemini** as a **Programmer / Developer Consultant**. During the program, I developed knowledge in several areas of interest required for this position, therefore, I strongly believe that I am a great fit.

I have a degree in Telecommunications Engineering in Brazil, with a 2-year exchange in Spain. This multilingual experience helped me to develop excellent communication skills. I am flexible to travel and look forward to working with talented people from all over the world.

As an engineer, I have worked in multinational companies, which has brought me extensive corporate experience, business knowledge and made me a problem-solving professional with excellent critical thinking who highly values teamwork, training, mentoring and collaborative environments.

I was also awarded for academic excellence, which proves my commitment, exceptional performance, perseverance and dedication. I am a specially organized person with proven leadership skills and ultimately a lover of process automation.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Technology Diploma

Centennial College, Toronto, Ontario, Canada

September 2019 – December 2021

GPA: 4.452 / 4.500

Relevant courses:

- API Engineering & Cloud Computing (.NET, AWS)
- Emerging Technologies (Mongoose, Express, React, Node.js)
- Web Application Development (.NET, JSON)
- Web Interface Design (JavaScript, HTML, CSS, UX and UI Design skills)
- Advanced Database Concepts (Oracle, PL/SQL, MongoDB)
- Java EE Programming (Java/J2EE)
- Networking for Software Developers (Python)

Bachelor of Telecommunications Engineering

Universidade Federal Fluminense, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

January 2004 – December 2011

GPA: 8.04 / 10.00

Bachelor of Telecommunications Engineering (exchange program)

September 2006 – June 2008

Universidad Politécnica de Madrid, Madrid, Spain

TECHNICAL SKILLS

•	JavaScript	•	.NET	•	MongoDB	•	Web Development
•	HTML & CSS	•	React	•	UX Design	•	Agile methodology
•	JSON	•	Express.js	•	UI Design	•	Excel Visual Basic
•	Database Oracle	•	Node.js	•	Java/J2EE	•	Google Colab
•	PL/SQL	•	Mongoose	•	MS Teams	•	Office365
•	AWS (S3, IAM, Elastic Beanstalk, DynamoDB, RDS, Lambda Functions, Step Functions)						

AWS Step Functions (https://github.com/claramagaldi/AWS-Step Functions.git)

A state machine (under AWS Step Functions) that is triggered by the upload of an image to a S3 bucket. It uses Lambda Functions to perform actions, such as extension check, label detection, save content into DynamoDB and S3 bucket.

ACADEMIC PROJECT WORK

Game Survey App (https://github.com/claramagaldi/Game-Survey.git)

An Express.js app that allows users to create game surveys. It is designed using a MVC structure, MongoDB database and EJS views.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior RF Engineer

Tim Brasil, Rio de Janeiro, RJ, Brazil

February 2014 - August 2019

https://site.tim.com.br/

I worked in the Mobile Access Engineering team focused on network quality. I was the leader of the segment responsible for the rollout projects of new sites (telecommunications towers). In this position, I developed organizational, leadership and data and project management skills. Having a creative mind, I took this opportunity to develop macros in Visual Basic that automate processes, reducing workloads for me and my colleagues. These Visual Basic projects processed data from different sources (some including Google APIs) to generate reporting and testing tools, analysis, and graphical solutions in order to assist us in making more accurate and consistent decisions.

Wireless Configuration Engineer

Láurea Acadêmica Award

Huawei Technologies, Rio de Janeiro, RJ, Brazil

April 2013 - January 2014

https://www.huawei.com/br/

Universidade Federal Fluminense · Jan 2012

At Huawei I worked with pre-sales on the Wireless product line for hardware, software and services solutions. In this job I started to develop my computer programming skills and created a Visual Basic tool to reduce human errors in the generation of pre-POS and BOQs. Subsequently, this code was studied by the company to assist in the development of an official tool.

HONORS AND AWARDS

Honours Designation: High HonoursCentennial College ⋅ Dec 2021Esther Whittingham ScholarshipCentennial College ⋅ Dec 2021 ⋅ \$1,000CCSAI Excellence in Academics and LeadershipCentennial College ⋅ Nov 2021 ⋅ \$2,000Centennial College Golf Merit ScholarshipCentennial College ⋅ Nov 2021 ⋅ \$2,000Distinction in LeadershipCentennial College ⋅ Jun 2021Esther Whittingham ScholarshipCentennial College ⋅ Jan 2021 ⋅ \$1,000

Clara Magaldi Rodrigues • github.com/claramagaldi • linkedin.com/in/clara-magaldi